<WarpSynkStewards>
    <Overview>
        WarpSynk Stewards are key participants in the WarpSynk ecosystem, designed to support, govern, and grow the decentralized data economy. They are early adopters, community leaders, and network guardians who play a critical role in shaping how WarpSynk operates.
    </Overview>
    <RolesAndResponsibilities>
        <Role>
            <Title>Governance Participation</Title>
            <Description>Stewards have voting power in the WarpSynk DAO, helping decide on protocol upgrades, initiatives, and community proposals.</Description>
        </Role>
        <Role>
            <Title>Network Oversight</Title>
            <Description>They monitor SynkNodes and the SynkMesh infrastructure to ensure smooth and secure operations.</Description>
        </Role>
        <Role>
            <Title>Community Engagement</Title>
            <Description>Stewards educate, onboard, and guide new users, spreading awareness of WarpSynk’s mission.</Description>
        </Role>
        <Role>
            <Title>Ecosystem Development</Title>
            <Description>They propose, support, and sometimes fund new projects or integrations within the WarpSynk network.</Description>
        </Role>
        <Role>
            <Title>Data Economy Leadership</Title>
            <Description>Stewards contribute to defining rules and practices that protect user privacy, security, and data ownership.</Description>
        </Role>
    </RolesAndResponsibilities>
    <Eligibility>
        <Requirement>Ownership of a Steward ID linked to a Steward Founder NFT</Requirement>
        <Requirement>Commitment to active participation in governance, community, and network activities</Requirement>
        <Requirement>Willingness to maintain and promote decentralized, private, and permissioned data interactions</Requirement>
    </Eligibility>
    <Incentives>
        <Incentive>
            <Title>Exclusive Access</Title>
            <Description>Stewards receive early access to protocol updates, beta tools, and ecosystem features.</Description>
        </Incentive>
        <Incentive>
            <Title>Financial Rewards</Title>
            <Description>They earn $WSYNK tokens for governance participation, network monitoring, and contributions to ecosystem growth.</Description>
        </Incentive>
        <Incentive>
            <Title>Recognition</Title>
            <Description>Steward status is public and linked to SynkPass NFTs, signaling credibility and influence in the WarpSynk community.</Description>
        </Incentive>
        <Incentive>
            <Title>Leadership Opportunities</Title>
            <Description>Stewards can propose initiatives, lead projects, or represent WarpSynk in partnerships.</Description>
        </Incentive>
    </Incentives>
    <WhyBecomeASteward>
        <Point>Influence the direction of the WarpSynk Protocol</Point>
        <Point>Gain early access to tools and opportunities in the decentralized data economy</Point>
        <Point>Participate in a community-driven project that values privacy, security, and user control over data</Point>
        <Point>Earn rewards and recognition while shaping the future of Web3 identity and data management</Point>
    </WhyBecomeASteward>
    <Conclusion>
        WarpSynk Stewards are more than participants; they are leaders, innovators, and protectors of a decentralized, user-controlled data ecosystem. They embody the mission of WarpSynk: giving individuals control over their digital identity, data, and economic value.
    </Conclusion>
</WarpSynkStewards>